

Profile

Front-end developer, knowledgeable in HTML, CSS and GIT. Experienced in collaborating with teams on different projects using GitHub. Passionate about designing responsive website. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

Employment History

Frontend developer (Intern) at TIIDELab

February 2022 — Present

- Building websites using HTML and CSS.
- Collaborated with team using GitHub ans git.
- Served as a dedicated and supportive Intern in a fast-paced environment.
- Effectively multi tasked and worked well with internal and external teams.
- Helped to achieve a consistent look and visual theme across the website by promoting uniform fonts, formatting, images, and layout.

★ Projects

Portfolio

March 2022 — March 2022

Built and hosted a personal portfolio on Netlify using HTML, CSS, Git/GitHub for CI/CD.

TiideCuisine (Meal App)

April 2022 — April 2022

- Worked with as a front end developer on a team. was responsible for building responsive header, footers and the modal section.
- Collaborated with team mates using GitHub and Git.

Education

Bachelor in Engineering, Federal University of Technology Minna

September 2015 — September 2021

Graduated with a second class division

Details

+2348051744986

faridasule24@gmail.com

Skills

CSS

Git

HTML

GitHub

Ability to Work in a Team